Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- P
  - X346 P183 I, 1859; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Samuel Palmer; London (Box 1307, Folder 8324)
  - lX346 P189, 1949 - 1967; nos. 5-74, 58 catalogs
    Location variant: København K., Denmark
    - Erik Paludan; København, Denmark (Box 1307, Folder 8325-8328)
    - Erik Paludan; København, Denmark (Box 1308, Folder 8329-8334)
    - Erik Paludan; København, Denmark (Box 1309, Folder 8335-8337)
  - X346 P1928, 1953 - 1968; nos. 9-42, 28 catalogs
    Location variant: Cambridge, Mass.
    - Pangloss Bookshop; New York, N. Y. (Box 1309, Folder 8338-8340)
    - Pangloss Bookshop; New York, N. Y. (Box 1310, Folder 8341-8343)
  - X346 P2125, 1948 - 1970; nos. 1-49, 30 catalogs
    - Paragon Book Gallery; New York, N. Y. (Box 1310, Folder 8344-8346)
    - Paragon Book Gallery; New York, N. Y. (Box 1311, Folder 8347-8353)
    - Paragon Book Gallery; New York, N. Y. (Box 1312, Folder 8354-8355)
  - X346 P214, 1922 - 1942; nos. 1-119, 94 catalogs
    - Libreria de Tomas Pardo; Buenos Aires (Box 1312, Folder 8356-8358)
  - X346 P214 I, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Libreria General de Tomas Pardo; Buenos Aires (Box 1312, Folder 8359)
  - X346 P2175, undated; nos. 1-45, 37 catalogs
    Name & location variant: Diana Parikian; Oxford, England
    - D. Parikian; London (Box 1313, Folder 8360-8365)
    - D. Parikian; London (Box 1314, Folder 8366-8368)
  - X346 P2238, 1771; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - C. Parker; [London] (Box 1314, Folder 8369)
  - X346 P2275, 1952 - 1974; unnumbered, 7 catalogs
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc.; New York (Box 1314, Folder 8370-8372)
  - X346 P229, undated; nos. 12-43, unnumbered, 25 lists 1 catalog
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1315, Folder 8373-8378)
  - X346 P229 I, undated, 1908-1974; unnumbered, nos. 3-279, 205 catalogs
    Name variant: Parker & Son, Ltd.
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1315, Folder 8379-8380)
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1316, Folder 8381-8386)
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1317, Folder 8387-8392)
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1318, Folder 8393-8399)
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1319, Folder 8400-8405)
    - Parker Son; Oxford (Box 1320, Folder 8406-8409)
  - X346 P2425, 1967-1968, undated; nos. 3-8, 4 catalogs
    - Parnassus Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 1320, Folder 8410)
  - X346 P2425 I, 1980 - 1981; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Parnassus Imprints; Yarmouth Port, Mass. (Box 1320, Folder 8411)
  - X346 P2675, 1964; nos. 1-11, 8 catalogs
    - Libreria Passim, S. A.; Barcelona, España (Box 1321, Folder 8412-8413)
  - X346 P275, 1961, undated; nos. 13-72, 28 catalogs
    - Joseph Patrick Books; Toronto, Canada (Box 1321, Folder 8414-8417)
  - X346 P291, 1748; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Thomas Payne; [London] (Box 1322, Folder 8418)
  - X346 P292, 1824 - 1842; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Payne and Foss; London (Box 1322, Folder 8419-8420)
  - X346 P317, undated; unnumbered, 44 catalogs
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1322, Folder 8421-8423)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1323, Folder 8424-8428)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1324, Folder 8429-8432)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1325, Folder 8433-8437)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1326, Folder 8438-8442)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1327, Folder 8443-8447)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1328, Folder 8448-8453)
    - J. Pearson Co.; London (Box 1329, Folder 8454)
  - X346 P317 I, undated, 1949-1951; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - John Pearson; London (Box 1329, Folder 8455)
  - X346 P317 II, undated; nos. 4-83, 24 catalogs
    Name variant: J. Pearson & Co.
    - John Pearson; London (Box 1329, Folder 8556-8460)
    - John Pearson; London (Box 1330, Folder 8461-8463)
  - X346 P317 III, undated; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - J. Pearson Co. (London), Ltd. (Box 1330, Folder 8464-8466)
    - J. Pearson Co. (London), Ltd. (Box 1331, Folder 8467-8469)
  - X346 P318, undated; unnumbered, nos. 3-21, 21 catalogs
    - R. C. Pearson, M.A.; Cambridge (Box 1331, Folder 8470-8471)
  - X346 P335, undated; nos.1-25, unnumbered, 26 catalogs
    - J. Ray Peck; New York, N. Y. (Box 1331, Folder 8472-8473)
  - X346 P344, 1956 - 1970; nos. 3-73, 34 catalogs
    - C. P. J. van der Peet; Amsterdam, Holland (Box 1332, Folder 8474-8480)
    - C. P. J. van der Peet; Amsterdam, Holland (Box 1333, Folder 8481-8482)
  - X346 P344 I, undated; nos. 109-230, 23 lists
    - C. P. J. van der Peet; Amsterdam, Holland (Box 1333, Folder 8483-8485)
  - X346 P345, [1958-1971]; nos. 151-994, 252 catalogs
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1333, Folder 8486-8487)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1334, Folder 8488-8493)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1335, Folder 8494-8499)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1336, Folder 8500-8505)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1337, Folder 8506-8511)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1338, Folder 8512-8517)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1339, Folder 8518-8524)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1340, Folder 8525-8530)
    - Jan Peet; Bussum and Amsterdam (Box 1341, Folder 8531-8532)
  - X346 P3495, 1952 - 1968; nos. 9-50, 39 catalogs
    Name variants: Libreria Antonio Sieso Peiro; Libreria A. Sieso Peiró
    - Libreria Atlántica de Antonio Sieso Peiro; Barcelona (Espana) (Box 1341, Folder 8533-8536)
    - Libreria Atlántica de Antonio Sieso Peiro; Barcelona (Espana) (Box 1342, Folder 8537-8542)
    - Libreria Atlántica de Antonio Sieso Peiro; Barcelona (Espana) (Box 1343, Folder 8543-8545)
  - X346 P35, 1730; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Anthony Peisley's Bookseller; Oxon (Box 1343, Folder 8546)
  - X346 P4419, 1952 - 1954; nos. 6-9, 4 catalogs
    - F. W. Peters; Berlin (Box 1343, Folder 8547-8548)
    - F. W. Peters; Berlin (Box 1344, Folder 8549-8550)
  - X346 P443, 1842 - 1858; nos. 9-207, 58 catalogs
    - John Petheram; London (Box 1344, Folder 8551-8553)
  - X346 P443 I, undated; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - John Petheram; London (Box 1344, Folder 8554)
  - X346 P446, undated; nos. 7-71, 47 catalogs
    - Librairie Lucien Petitot; Paris (Box 1344, Folder 8555-8556)
    - Librairie Lucien Petitot; Paris (Box 1345, Folder 8557-8563)
    - Librairie Lucien Petitot; Paris (Box 1346, Folder 8564-8565)
  - X346 P485, 1935-1936, undated; nos. 2-6, 5 catalogs
    - Arthur Pforzheimer; New York (Box 1346, Folder 8566)
  - X346 P535, 1862 - 1864; nos. 9-25, 17 catalogs
    - Geo. P. Philes Co.; New York (Box 1346, Folder 8567-8571)
  - X346 P546, 1984; no. 524, 1 catalog
    - Phillips, Son Neale, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1346, Folder 8572)
  - X346 P575, 1890 - 1975; nos. 47-421, 268 catalogs
    Name variants: Alphonse Picard & Fils; A. Picard; A. et J. Picard. Nos. 106-120 bound together
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1346, Folder 8573-8574)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1347, Folder 8575-8580)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1348, Folder 8581-8587)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1349, Folder 8588-8594)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1350, Folder 8595-8601)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1351, Folder 8602-8607)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1352, Folder 8608-8613)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1353, Folder 8614-8619)
    - Alphonse Picard; Paris (Box 1354, Folder 8620)
  - X346 P575 II, 1920 - 1940; unnumbered, 18 catalogs
    - Librairie Auguste Picard; Paris (Box 1354, Folder 8621-8625)
  - X346 P58, 1870-[1875?]; nos. 104-121, 22 catalogs
    Includes six unnumbered catalogs.
    - Pickering Co.; London (Box 1354, Folder 8626)
    - Pickering Co.; London (Box 1355, Folder 8627-8629)
  - X346 P58 I, 1889 - 1986; nos. 29-661, 249 catalogs
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1355, Folder 8630-8633)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1356, Folder 8634-8639)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1357, Folder 8640-8645)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1358, Folder 8646-8651)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1359, Folder 8652-8657)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1360, Folder 8658-8663)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1361, Folder 8664-8669)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1362, Folder 8670-8675)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1363, Folder 8676-8680)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1364, Folder 8681-8686)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1365, Folder 8687-8692)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1366, Folder 8693-8697)
  - X346 P58 II, undated; unnumbered, 30 catalogs
    Miscellaneous catalogs.
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1367, Folder 8698-8703)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1368, Folder 8704-8708)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1369, Folder 8709-8713)
    - Pickering Chatto; London (Box 1370, Folder 8714-8715)
  - X346 P6515, undated; nos. 1-6, 5 catalogs
    - Librairie L. et J.-H. Pinault; Paris (Box 1370, Folder 8716)
  - X346 P6565, undated; nos. 84-113, 5 catalogs
    - Pinkus Co; Zürich (Box 1370, Folder 8717-8718)
  - X346 P757, 1946 - 1954; nos. 20-52, 21 catalogs
    Location variant: Ablon
    - Librairie Charles Poisson; Paris (Box 1370, Folder 8719-8720)
    - Librairie Charles Poisson; Paris (Box 1371, Folder 8721)
  - X346 P7575, 1955 - 1970; nos. 30-45, 10 catalogs
    - Jean Polak Libraire; Paris (Box 1371, Folder 8722)
  - X346 P759, undated; nos. 12-28, 8 catalogs
    - IL Polifilo; Milano (Box 1371, Folder 8723-8725)
  - X346 P759 I, undated; nos. 26-60, 30 lists
    - IL Polifilo; Milano (Box 1371, Folder 8726-8728)
    - IL Polifilo; Milano (Box 1372, Folder 8729-8730)
  - X346 P771, undated; nos. 8-30, 19 catalogs
    - M. Pomarin; Brooklyn, N.Y. (Box 1372, Folder 8731-8733)
  - X346 P796, 1948 - 1961; nos. 7-80, 21 lists
    - Poona Oriental Book House; Poona, India (Box 1372, Folder 8734)
  - X346 P816, 1911 - 1939; nos. 1-54, 18 catalogs
    - Karl Max Poppe; Leipzig (Box 1373, Folder 8735-8739)
  - X346 P8165, undated; nos. 2-6, 5 catalogs
    - Porpoise Bookshop; San Francisco, California (Box 1373, Folder 8740)
  - X346 P828, 1934 - 1954; nos. 1-16, 15 catalogs
    - Jose Porrua e Hijos; Mexico D.F. (Box 1373, Folder 8741-8742)
    - Jose Porrua e Hijos; Mexico D.F. (Box 1374, Folder 8743-8748)
  - X346 P828 I, 1913 - 1951; various numberings, 102 catalogs
    - Porrua Hermanos; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1375, Folder 8749-8766)
    - Porrua Hermanos; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1376, Folder 8767)
  - X346 P828 II, [ca. 1940]-1952; various numberings, 35 catalogs
    - Antigua Libreria Robredo; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1376, Folder 8768-8772)
    - Antigua Libreria Robredo; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1377, Folder 8773-8775)
  - X346 P828 VI, 1957 - 1967; nos. 1-13, 8 catalogs
    - Jose Porrua Turanzas; Madrid (Box 1377, Folder 8776-8778)
  - X346 P8281, 1948 - 1967; various numberings, 19 catalogs
    - Libreria de Manuel Porrua; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1377, Folder 8779-8780)
    - Libreria de Manuel Porrua; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1378, Folder 8781-8782)
  - X346 P8281 II, 1948-1953, undated; nos. 1-6, 5 catalogs
    - Libreria de Manuel Porrua; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1378, Folder 8783-8785)
  - X346 P8281 III, 1950; nos. [1]-6, 4 catalogs
    - Librería de Manuel Porrúa; Mexico, D.F. (Box 1378, Folder 8786)
  - X346 P834, undated, 1933, undated; nos. 1-47
    - José Porter Librero; Barcelona (Box 1379, Folder 8787)
  - X346 P834 I, undated; nos. 3-8, 4 catalogs
    - Llibrería de Josep Porté; Barcelona (Box 1379, Folder 8788)
  - X346 P834 II, 1949 - 1961; nos. 6-15, 10 catalogs
    - José Porter Librero; Barcelona (Box 1379, Folder 8789-8790)
  - X346 P834 III, undated, 1955-1958; nos. 1-6, 8 catalogs
    - José Porter Librero; Barcelona (Box 1379, Folder 8791)
  - X346 P834 IV, 1956 - 1963; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Jose Porter Librero; Barcelona (Box 1379, Folder 8792-8793)
  - X346 P8385, 1956 - 1961; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Livraria Portugal; Lisboa (Box 1380, Folder 8794-8795)
  - X346 P8385 I, 1951 - 1986; nos. 91-526, 260 catalogs
    Name variant: Livraria Portugal
    - Livraria Portugália; Lisboa (Box 1380, Folder 8796-8800)
    - Livraria Portugália; Lisboa (Box 1381, Folder 8801-8807)
    - Livraria Portugália; Lisboa (Box 1382, Folder 8808-8813)
    - Livraria Portugália; Lisboa (Box 1383, Folder 8814-8819)
    - Livraria Portugália; Lisboa (Box 1384, Folder 8820-8821)
  - X346 P8465, undated; nos. 10-27, 13 catalogs
    - G. Postima; Amsterdam (Box 1384, Folder 8822)
  - X346 P856, 1912 - 1935; no. 179, unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - William Potter; Liverpool (Box 1384, Folder 8823)
  - X346 P867, 1939-[1971]; nos. 1-323, 227 catalogs
    - André Poursin; Paris (Box 1384, Folder 8824-8826)
    - André Poursin; Paris (Box 1385, Folder 8827-8833)
    - André Poursin; Paris (Box 1386, Folder 8834-8839)
    - André Poursin; Paris (Box 1387, Folder 8840-8842)
  - X346 P876, 1939 - 1956; nos. 1-15, 13 catalogs
    - Librairie M. Poyer; Paris (Box 1387, Folder 8843)
  - X346 P877, 1901 - 1906; nos. 17-38, 35 catalogs
    - G.A. Poynder; Reading (Box 1387, Folder 8844)
    - G.A. Poynder; Reading (Box 1388, Folder 8845-8847)
  - X346 P877 I, 1900 - 1923; nos. 14-90, 16 catalogs
    - G.A. Poynder; Reading, Berks., Eng. (Box 1388, Folder 8848-8849)
  - X346 P8855, 1957 - 1963; nos. 91-123, 9 catalogs
    - Libreria Prandi; Reggio Emilia (Box 1388, Folder 8850)
    - Libreria Prandi; Reggio Emilia (Box 1389, Folder 8851)
  - X346 P913, 1962 - 1983; nos. 1-49, 27 catalogs
    - Libreria Antiquaria Pregliasco; Torino (Box 1389, Folder 8852-8856)
    - Libreria Antiquaria Pregliasco; Torino (Box 1390, Folder 8857)
  - X346 P913 I, 1967 - 1983; unnumbered, 10 catalogs
    - Libreria Antiquaria Pregliasco; Torino (Italia) (Box 1390, Folder 8858-8859)
  - X346 P9135, 1967 - 1968; nos. 1-5, 5 catalogs
    - Giorgina Pregliasco-Mathes; Torino (Box 1390, Folder 8860)
  - X346 P927, 1952 - 1964; nos. 145-178, 33 catalogs
    - Preston Book Company; Preston, Lancs. (Box 1390, Folder 8861-8863)
  - X346 P931, undated; nos. 131-134, 3 lists
    - C.D. Price, Inc.; Cherry Hill, N.J. (Box 1391, Folder 8864)
  - X345 P9325, 1787; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - William Prichard; Philadelphia (Box 1391, Folder 8865)
  - X345 P933, 1813; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Mary Priestley; [London] (Box 1391, Folder 8866)
  - X346 P934, 1809 - 1823; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - Richard Priestley; London (Box 1391, Folder 8867-8870)
    - Richard Priestley; London (Box 1392, Folder 8871)
  - X346 P936, 1776; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Daniel Prince; Oxford (Box 1392, Folder 8872)
  - X346 P939, 1921 - 1963; nos. 113-331, 126 catalogs
    - Georges Privat; Paris (Box 1392, Folder 8873-8878)
    - Georges Privat; Paris (Box 1393, Folder 8879-8884)
    - Georges Privat; Paris (Box 1394, Folder 8885-8891)
  - X346 P940, 1954-1955, undated; various numberings, 16 catalogs
    - Pro-libris; Barcelona (Box 1395, Folder 8892-8895)
  - X346 P947, 1962 - 1993; unnumbered, 41 catalogs
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1395, Folder 8896-8898)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1396, Folder 8899-8904)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1397, Folder 8905-8910)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1398, Folder 8911-8919)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1399, Folder 8920-8926)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1400, Folder 8927-8934)
    - Paul Prouté et ses fils; Paris (Box 1401, Folder 8935)
  - X346 P979, [1910-1944]; nos. 1-8, 3 catalogs
    - G.P. Putnam's Sons; London (Box 1401, Folder 8936)
  - X346 P9791, [1971]; no. 116, 1 catalog
    - Putnam Bookshop; Bloomington, Illinois (Box 1401, Folder 8937)
  - X346 P9895, [1969-1974]; nos. 11-38, 17 catalogs
    - Libreria Puvill; Barcelona (Box 1401, Folder 8938-8940)
  - X346 P9895 I, 1952 - 1986; nos. 34-180, 116 catalogs
    Name variant: Puvill Libros. Also includes two unnumbered catalogs.
    - Libreria Puvill; Barcelona (Box 1401, Folder 8941-8944)
    - Libreria Puvill; Barcelona (Box 1402, Folder 8945-8950)
    - Libreria Puvill; Barcelona (Box 1403, Folder 8951-8956)
    - Libreria Puvill; Barcelona (Box 1404, Folder 8957-8959)
- Q
  - X346 Q27, 1860 - 1915; 22 catalogs in 42 bound volumes
    Many catalogs incomplete. Includes catalogs, prospecti, desiderata. Also includes some supplements
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1405, Folder 8960-8963)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1406, Folder 8964)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1407, Folder 8965)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1408, Folder 8966)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1409, Folder 8967)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1410, Folder 8968-8971)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1411, Folder 8972-8975)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1412, Folder 8976-8979)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1413, Folder 8980-8982)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1414, Folder 8983)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1415, Folder 8984)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1416, Folder 8985)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1417, Folder 8986)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1418, Folder 8987)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1419, Folder 8988)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1420, Folder 8989)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1421, Folder 8990-8995)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1422, Folder 8996-8999)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1423, Folder 9000-9004)
  - X346 Q27 2, 1867 - 1980; 70 catalogs
    Miscellaneous catalogs including several auction catalogs, some bound volumes. Includes duplicates
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1424, Folder 9005-9011)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1425, Folder 9012-9017)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1426, Folder 9018-9023)
  - X346 Q27a, 1855 - 1859; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1426, Folder 9024)
  - X346 Q27b, 1864 - 1887; nos. 213-375, 111 catalogs
    Monthly catalogs including indexes. Index to to nos. 279-291a is a photostat
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1427, Folder 9025-9030)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1428, Folder 9031)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1429, Folder 9032-9037)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1430, Folder 9038)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1431, Folder 9039-9044)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1432, Folder 9045-9050)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1433, Folder 9051)
  - X346 Q27c, 1886 - 1891; nos. 3-61, 15 catalogs
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1433, Folder 9052-9057)
  - X346 Q27d, 1870 - 1986; nos. 5-1062, 961 catalogs
    Includes supplements and duplicates. Some catalogs in bound volumes. Name variant: Bernard Quaritch Ltd.
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1434, Folder 9058-9063)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1435, Folder 9064-9069)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1436, Folder 9070-9074)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1437, Folder 9075-9080)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1438, Folder 9081-9086)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1439, Folder 9087-9091)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1440, Folder 9092-9097)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1441, Folder 9098-9103)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1442, Folder 9104-9109)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1443, Folder 9110-9115)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1444, Folder 9116-9122)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1445, Folder 9123-9129)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1446, Folder 9130-9135)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1447, Folder 9136-9141)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1448, Folder 9142-9147)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1449, Folder 9148-9153)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1450, Folder 9154-9159)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1451, Folder 9160-9165)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1452, Folder 9166-9171)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1453, Folder 9172-9176)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1454, Folder 9177-9182)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1455, Folder 9183-9188)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1456, Folder 9189-9194)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1457, Folder 9195-9200)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1458, Folder 9201-9206)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1459, Folder 9207-9212)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1460, Folder 9213-9218)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1461, Folder 9219-9224)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1462, Folder 9225-9230)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1463, Folder 9231-9236)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1464, Folder 9237-9242)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1465, Folder 9243-9248)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1466, Folder 9249-9254)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1467, Folder 9255-9260)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1468, Folder 9261-9266)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1469, Folder 9267-9272)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1470, Folder 9273-9278)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1471, Folder 9279-9284)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1472, Folder 9285-2290)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1473, Folder 2291-9296)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1474, Folder 9297-9302)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1475, Folder 9303-9308)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1476, Folder 9309-9314)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1477, Folder 9315-9317)
    - Bernard Quaritch; London (Box 1478, Folder 9318)
  - X346 Q35, 1921 - 1937; nos. 5-126, 93 catalogs
    Name variant: J.A. Quereuil, Libraire
    - Librairie J.-A. Quereuil; Paris (Box 1478, Folder 9319-9323)
    - Librairie J.-A. Quereuil; Paris (Box 1479, Folder 9324-9329)
    - Librairie J.-A. Quereuil; Paris (Box 1480, Folder 9330-9332)
  - X346 Q35 I, 1934 - 1936; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Librairie Ancienne J.-A. Quereuil; Paris (Box 1480, Folder 9333)
  - X346 Q45, 1935; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - James A. Quinn; New York City (Box 1480, Folder 9334)
- R
  - X346 R1, undated; nos. 113-148, 4 catalogs
    - R and D Books; Washington, D.C. (Box 1481, Folder 9335-9336)
  - X346 R158, 1977 - 1981; nos. 1-70, 13 catalogs
    Name variants: Randall House; Ravenstreet Company
    - Randall Windle; San Francisco, CA (Box 1481, Folder 9337-9339)
    - Randall Windle; San Francisco, CA (Box 1482, Folder 9340-9341)
  - X346 R181 I, 1884 - 1892; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Librairie de Rapilly; Paris (Box 1482, Folder 9342-9343)
  - X346 R181 II, 1894 - 1938; nos. 6-308, 193 catalogs
    Name variants: Librairie Georges Rapilly; G. Rapilly & Fils
    - Georges Rapilly; Paris (Box 1482, Folder 9344-9345)
    - Georges Rapilly; Paris (Box 1483, Folder 9346-9351)
    - Georges Rapilly; Paris (Box 1484, Folder 9352-9361)
    - Georges Rapilly; Paris (Box 1485, Folder 9362-9365)
  - X346 R182, undated; nos. 5-152, 97 catalogs
    Location variant: Roma
    - C. E. Rappaport; Rome (Box 1485, Folder 9366-9367)
    - C. E. Rappaport; Rome (Box 1486, Folder 9368-9373)
    - C. E. Rappaport; Rome (Box 1487, Folder 9374-9380)
    - C. E. Rappaport; Rome (Box 1488, Folder 9381-9386)
    - C. E. Rappaport; Rome (Box 1489, Folder 9387-9389)
  - X346 R1915, 1948 - 1961; nos. 1-7, 10 catalogs
    - Nicolas Rauch; Geneve (Box 1489, Folder 9390-9392)
    - Nicolas Rauch; Geneve (Box 1490, Folder 9393-9396)
  - X346 R1915 II, 1950 - 1962; nos. 1-8, 8 bulletins
    - Nicolas Rauch; Geneve (Box 1490, Folder 9397)
    - Nicolas Rauch; Geneve (Box 1491, Folder 9398)
  - X346 R192, 1954 - 1960; nos. 9-27, 4 catalogs
    - Nicolas Rauch; Geneve (Box 1491, Folder 9399)
  - X346 R193, 1873; nos. 51-478, 55 catalogs
    Name variants: Schweizer Antiquariat; Hellmut Schumann AG. Includes 13 catalogs bound in 1 volume
    - Albert Raustein; Zurich (Box 1491, Folder 9400-9402)
    - Albert Raustein; Zurich (Box 1492, Folder 9403-9408)
    - Albert Raustein; Zurich (Box 1493, Folder 9409-9411)
  - X346 R196, 1936-[1970]; nos. 5-412, 61 catalogs
    - Raven Book Shop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1493, Folder 9412-9413)
    - Raven Book Shop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1494, Folder 9414-9419)
    - Raven Book Shop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1495, Folder 9420)
  - X346 R1973, [1969]-1983; nos. 2-96, 134 catalogs